Today, I'm going to show you guys how
we're able to turn Claude into a
one-person marketing team. You don't
have to be technical at all. You don't
have to know how to edit videos or edit
photos or anything like that. You just
have to know what to ask for. I'm not
going to make any assumptions today. I'm
going to assume that we're starting at
the beginning and you haven't used these
tools before. So, let's not waste any
time and just get straight into the
video. All right. So, before we get into
the tools, let me just explain what
we're doing here. So, step one is going
to be the project. I'm going to help you
guys get set up on Claude Code, help you
guys get set up with the actual like
files and folders that you need, and
then we're going to be off to the races.
Then we have to go ahead and set up
Higgs Field and get that connected. So,
I'll show you what that all looks like.
And then finally, what we have to do is
actually start generating assets and
showing you how this all is going to
evolve over time. So, before we get into
the project, let me show you what we're
working with for the sake of today's
example. So, in the video today, I'm
going to be using Perk Form as an
example, which is my fake business. All
of these assets you're about to see, by
the way, were generated by Claude and
Higgs Field together. So, here are our
logos. We have text, we have light mode,
we have dark mode, we have the actual
logo, which is pretty cool cuz this is
like a coffee protein energy drink. And
we've got like a coffee bean with a
lightning bolt. So, pretty clever. I
didn't ask for that, right? I just asked
for a logo and it did this. So, pretty
cool. Anyways, here's the product. We
have um these drinks. It looks like an
energy drink, right? We've got vanilla,
latte, salted caramel, and bold mocha.
You can see we have individual product
shots as well as studio product shots.
These were all created with GPT Image 2,
which is a AI image model, which I'll
talk more about a little bit. But what's
really the most important thing is what
I call the AI monetization readiness
assessment, which is you guys probably
are all here because you have maybe a
business or you want to offer things to
clients, like offer AI marketing to
clients. And
what you need is you need these three
things, the three Ps.
You need a pain, you need a person, and
you need a promise. So, what is the pain
that your business is trying to solve?
Who is the person, specifically, that
feels that pain? And then how does your
brand or product or service promise to
solve that pain for that person? So,
that's exactly what you need in order to
even get a project like this set up in
the first place, and you need all this
stuff to make sure that your marketing
assets don't look and feel like generic
AI slop. They have to have a purpose,
they have to have intent behind it. And
so, setting up this kind of stuff is
really important. And that's exactly why
we're actually using Claude Code with
Higgsfield today. Because what
Higgsfield is is it is a AI tool that
has a bunch of different models and
things that you can do in here. So, it's
got C Dance 2.5, which is a really good
video model that you can only get early
access on Higgsfield. It's got other
video models here as you can see. It's
got Gemini, it's got Kling, it's got
Flux, it's got Sora. If we go to images,
it's got GBT Image 2, which is how you
saw those assets earlier, these ones.
These were all generated with GBT Image
2. It's got other ones, too, of course,
and, you know, Nano Banana, Grok. It's
got a bunch of different models all in
one subscription. So, that's why we're
going to be connecting it to
Claude today. It's also got something
called a marketing studio, which is
really cool. You can basically have your
assets be turned into ad creatives or
sizzle reels or whatever you want. You
can use these templates and
the AI models on the back end power it
all. And the reason why we want to use
Claude for this is because yes, you
could just open up Higgsfield and do all
that yourself, but if we use Claude, we
can set up a whole project. And now we
have a project that understands the
context of our business. We can set up
reusable skills, which are basically
just like recipes, workflows, so that if
you want an Instagram carousel, it's
always done in that same way. If you
want a UDC ad, it's always done in that
same way. So, skills help us create
things that scale. And then we can set
guidelines, like our actual brand
guidelines. So, for example, for
Perkform, here are the brand guidelines.
We have, you know, the color scheme, we
have what the brand is looking to do, we
have the logo system, we have the
typography, we have all this kind of
stuff. And this is probably something
that you want to have for your business
that you can give to Claude so that
every time it makes different assets or
different deliverables, it follows those
brand guidelines. So, for Perkform, for
example, these are the three P's and
this is the type of information that
we're going to feed into Claude. The
person is a busy fitness-minded
professional who relies on coffee, cares
about protein, and frequently rushes
through breakfast. Their pain is that in
their mornings, it requires too many
separate products like coffee, protein
shake, and something portable. And the
promise is that
and their protein in one grab-and-go
can, making it easier to start energized
and stay on track. So, that's the
information that we have, very baseline
high-level information that we have
right now about Perk form.
So, what I want you guys to do is you're
probably in a place where you have
either a physical product or you've got,
you know, a SaaS or whatever it is, but
you probably have a business and a logo
ready to go. Now, if you don't, what I
would do real quick is go ahead and get
some. So, whether you have real product
shots already or, you have just a name,
just go over to Higgsfield, create an
account, that's going to be step one,
and then just go ahead and go to like
image and create an image. And all you
have to do here is choose your model. I
would probably use GPT image 2,
honestly, and just ask for a logo. So,
real quick, let me just say, "Hey, I've
got a SaaS product called
um
Calendly, and I want to get a quick logo
for this
drafted up. It is a, you know, online
calendar booking appointment sort of
SaaS." And then you click generate and
it will go ahead and pop that over for
you right here. You can see some of
these other generations, they're very
high-quality images. We also have like
this sort of like storyboard for a UGC
ad. It has a lot that can go on here.
And right now, this was obviously a
prompt that I just put in, but the idea
is once you start to set up all this
context and stuff, and you connect
Higgsfield to Claude, Claude will do all
the prompting, Claude will do all the
navigation of this UI. So, at the end of
the day, you actually will never have to
be inside of Higgsfield navigating the
UI. You just ask Claude for things and
it goes and does it. And while this is
loading up, let's go ahead and get set
up with Claude code. So, you're going to
go to Google and type in Claude code
desktop. You'll scroll down to this link
and basically just install this for your
operating system. It's going to look the
same as if you've used Claude or like
ChatGPT in the web. It's very, very
similar. It basically just looks like
this. You can see that I can type in my
chats right here. I can choose like a
folder to work in, and that's going to
be a big unlock here between Claude Code
and Claude. Just because it has the word
code, don't think that we're going to be
coding. Like I said, you don't have to
be technical at all. The reason why
we're using Claude Code is because
Claude Code works out of directories,
out of projects. So, like in here, what
we're going to do is we're going to set
up a new folder together, and I'm going
to help you guys set up this folder so
that every time you use this project,
Claude Code gets smarter and smarter and
knows more and more about your business.
So, that's going to be super helpful.
So, just to show you guys a quick
example of how I did this with Claude
Code, this is the Perk Form brand, and
basically I gave it this idea and said,
"Hey, I have this brand called Perk
Form. It's going to be, you know,
coffee, protein, energy drinks. And what
I need you to do is go create me
a bunch of assets. I need product shots
cuz I had no product shots at this
point. I need product shots, I need
studio shots, I need logos, I need brand
guidelines, and it created all of these
folders for me. So, brand guidelines, it
created these assets with logos, with
packaging, with product shots, as you
guys saw. It created all of this and
just put it right here into my actual
desktop. And now I can work inside of
this project to create more assets in
the future. So, as you can see, it just
made this Calendly logo. Obviously, this
isn't anything too crazy because I
prompted it very simply. But, that's
basically all it is. That's how you come
in here, you can ask for an image, you
can ask for a video, and if you need to
get a few of these base things set up to
feel more comfortable before we actually
hop into like setting up the rest of the
project, then you can go ahead and do
that. Or you can just continue to follow
along and then fill in the gaps later as
you need. So, the next step is I want
you to create a new folder on your
desktop somewhere. So, I'm doing it
inside of a folder called Claude Code
YouTube. So, don't get intimidated
because I have all these other projects
here. But, we're just going to create a
new folder, and I'm going to call this
one um Perk Form Marketing. You can call
it whatever you want. And then, what's
in here is I'm going to show you it's
it's going to be nothing in here. So, if
I open up that Perk Form Marketing,
there's nothing in there. So, this is
what we're going to open up in Claude
Code, and we'll all be starting at
pretty much the same place. So, open up
Claude. Once you've downloaded that,
you're going to sign in with your
subscription, and then you're going to
start a new chat. And right down here,
it'll say local. That just basically
means that right now we're running
Claude on our computer.
It says a folder right here which we can
choose. So, you're going to click on
open folder, and you're just going to
navigate to that one that we were just
looking at, the one that you just
created. So, wherever you stored that,
go ahead and open that up. So, it's my
new one right here. I'm selecting that
folder. I'm going to hit trust workspace
because it's going to be able to read
inside of that folder, add files, edit
them, move them around, things like
that. And now we're pretty much ready to
get started. We have to create something
called a claude.md, which is basically
just instructions for this project. So,
like, "Hey, you know, here's I'm Nate. I
own this business called Perk Form, and
here's what I want to do inside this
project." That's what we need to build.
And basically, you just do all this with
natural language. So, here's what I'm
going to say.
Hey, so my name is Nate. I run a
business called Perk Form. It is a
energy drink company, but the energy
drinks are like coffee flavors, and they
also have protein in them. And I'm going
to give you some information about the
business so that you can help save this
as context for the project because what
I want you to do ultimately is you're
kind of going to be like my marketing
team. You're going to help me generate
things like ads or a website or UGC
content. You're going to help me
generate those types of things. So, you
understanding my business and the
motivations and the avatar and things
like that are going to help out a lot
when you're creating this kind of stuff.
So, I'm going to [snorts] dump in a
bunch of information for you, and I need
you to create me a claude.md file as
well as any other context files that you
think are relevant that you can
reference later.
So, basically just say something like
that, and it will know what to do. And
then, your job now is to dump in some
context about your business. I
definitely recommend dumping in
something about these three P's. That's
going to be really important for
marketing, but also anything else that
you want to share about your business.
So, right here what I'm going to do is
paste in a bunch of information. I
pasted in things like our three P's. I
pasted in some more info about the
business, our marketing angles, things
like that. And I'm going to go ahead and
just run that. And so, when you talk to
Claude Code, don't be intimidated. All
it does is it tells you right here what
it's thinking and what it's doing. So,
we'll see that there's a spinning, we're
seeing that it's thinking, it's going to
tell us when it creates files, and it's
going to tell us all these things. Now,
if you want to have visibility into what
it's doing from a file perspective,
click up here, three dots, click on
files, and you can see right now the
entire folder is empty. But as it starts
to create other folders or other assets
for us, it will fill them in right here.
And if you guys are feeling like you
don't know what type of information to
give it or you're a little bit Let me
show you guys a quick tip. So, remember
earlier when I said skills, I mentioned
that these are kind of like reusable
workflows or recipes that you can save.
These are helpful in multiple ways, not
just for creating content. So, I have a
skill right here called the Grill Me.
And if I open up the skill, you can see
it's basically just a prompt. It's a big
markdown file. And the point of the
skill is to relentlessly interview the
user about every aspect of a topic until
you reach shared understanding. So,
essentially, getting everything in your
brain into the agent's brain. And the
agent will keep digging in and asking
questions until it feels satisfied. So,
what you can do is you can grab this
skill. I'll put it inside of my free
school community. The link for that is
in the description. Completely free.
You'll come into here and you'll click
on classroom, and then you will go to
all YouTube resources and download the
skill. It'll just be like a markdown
file. And then all you have to do is you
would literally come into your Claude,
you would drag the skill into the chat,
and it would look at it right here, and
then you'd say, "Hey, this is a skill
called Grill Me. Go ahead and install
this inside of this project so I can use
it." And then once you install it, just
run the Grill Me skill on my product and
my marketing so you understand like
how I think about marketing my product.
And then it will literally just
interview you, ask you questions one by
one, and it will save that interview so
later it has all that context. So,
that's a really helpful thing that you
can do. But like I said, now it's
basically just going to build up
everything inside of this project. So,
I'll check in with you guys when this is
done, and I'll analyze and tell you
about what just happened and why it's
important. Okay, so you can see that
that is now done. First thing you'll
notice on the right-hand side, we have a
few things over here. We have a
Claude.md, we have an output folder
that's empty, we have a context folder
that has some stuff in here, and we have
an assets folder that's also empty. So,
we'll analyze all this. Just give me a
sec. The context base is built. Here's
what's in the folder. So, the Claude.md,
this is the operating doc. It tells any
future session what this project is,
what to load, what to look at, things
like that. We also have things like the
three P's inside of a brand positioning
doc. We have the custom avatar, we have
product facts, voice and copy, message
bank, playbooks, landscape, and it also
created extra folders because it knows
that we're going to have to put in some
like logos, pictures, and it's also
going to create deliverables which will
go in the output folder. So, that's what
we're looking at. We're going to drop in
logos and pictures in the assets.
Whenever it creates things for us, it
will put them in the output folder, and
then we have all of these files. So,
just to show you what those look like.
The Claude.md, let me just open this up
a little bit. You can see if you read
this, it's very, very simple. This is
the marketing project for Perk Form. A
canned protein coffee brand. Nate Herk
owns this business. Read these files
before writing anything. So, it will
It's telling it inside of here, if you
need context on any of this, you go to
these files. So, it's basically just
giving the information. It's setting the
scene of this project. That's what the
Claude.md is for. This is something that
you'll probably change every day, every
week as you're learning more
information, as you're adding more
stuff. Just say, "Hey Claude, by the
way, add that to the Claude.md. This is
important." I'm not going to look at all
of these, but for example, if I go to
the brand positioning, you can see this
is once again another markdown file
where we have things like the real
opportunity, the three P's, the
positioning statement, the promise. We
have all of these things that will get
worked into our messaging in the ads or
in any of the creatives, right? Because
it's not a gym bro brand. It's not a
meal replacement. Here's what it really
is. So, we want to make sure that we're
not marketing it in the wrong way, and
now Claude has all of this context.
Okay, cool. So, hopefully that makes
sense at this point. Let's start to
figure out how do we actually start
building some assets? So, what you need
to do now is give this some
meat, right? Give it some logos and
stuff. So, what I'm going to do is I'm
going to open up the actual um
folder that has all of our assets, and
I'm going to start to put them into
here. Okay, so here's what I'm going to
do. Try to not make it confusing. So,
remember right here inside of our
project, we have all of these folders
and files. Well, those actually exist
still in our desktop in my file
explorer. So, you can see assets,
context, output, Claude, open questions.
That's what we're looking at over here.
Now, on this right side, this is some
assets and stuff that we want to add in
to our project. So, you can see I've got
these four logos, which I'm just going
to drag into the assets right there.
Okay, there we go. I'm also going to put
in the product shots. And I'm actually
just going to take this whole folder and
move that into the assets workspace. And
you don't have to necessarily move them.
You could always make a copy and put the
copy in there. However, you want to just
fill up your current Claude code project
with some of this information. And then
the last thing I want to add over is our
actual brand guidelines. And so, that
would be right here in the brand
guidelines. It's just a PDF, and I'm
going to grab that. And once again, I'm
going to move that into our assets
folder. So, now what you see is back in
our Claude code project, we have all of
those things in here. We have um it
looks like we have these logos, we have
these product shots. Some of them are
probably still loading in, but we're
starting to get stuff actually inside of
our project. Now, I am noticing
something weird. Right here you can see
the product shots is coming through as a
it like it's supposed to be a folder,
but it's not being able to be read for
some reason. Over here you can see that
this is basically our assets folder, and
we have product shot folder in it with
all the product shots, but they're not
coming through. So, what I want to do is
I just want to verify if Claude can
actually see that. So, when you're in a
situation like this where you're a
little confused, just ask Claude what it
sees.
Hey, so inside of the assets folder in
this project, I dragged in another
folder called product shots, but it's
kind of appearing weird. So, I want to
know, can you actually see all of the
product shots that are inside of that
folder? There should be 11 of them in
there. And so, what you can do is you
can see that it's reading the files to
look. And you can see that it is able to
read all of these actual PNGs. It can
see them. So, it's just appearing a
little bit weird on this right-hand
side. That might just be a bug right
now, or maybe it needs to like refresh.
But, what we're showing though is Claude
is proving to us that it can actually
see these, and it's reading them, as you
can see right over here. Cool. So, it
said, "Yes, all 11 are there. Here's the
inventory." Awesome. So, we have now
confirmed that Claude can actually see
that stuff. So, here's what I want to do
now. The first thing that we want to get
set up is we want to set up a website.
And we want to make this a really cool
website for our product. So, what I'm
going to do is I'm going to drop this
link in the description. This is called
Scroll World. It's a super cool GitHub
repo that was made by this guy named
Oso, and it creates websites for us that
kind of have this feel where we scroll
in um this isn't loading right now. But,
you guys will see what I mean. It's
very, very cool. And we use Claude code
with this, as well as with Higgsfield,
to generate the videos. And then it's
like a 3D interactive website. So, let's
just go ahead and start building it. If
you haven't yet went to Higgsfield and
created an account, go ahead and create
an account, sign up, get on a plan. Now,
once you are in your Higgsfield account,
all you have to do is at the top, go to
this button that says MCP and CLI. And
the first one you see right here is
called Claude. So, all you have to do is
copy this URL. You're then going to go
into Claude. You're going to click on
customize. You're going to go to
connectors. You're going to add a custom
connector. And you're just going to
paste that in right there, and then just
call it Higgsfield. And then hit add.
Now, once that happens, it will pop up
something like this, and all you have to
do now is sign in. So, you'll hit
connect to Claude. It's going to take
you to Higgsfield, and you will have to
sign in with the account that you
already made. There you go. And then
you'll basically just give it
permission. So, you'll allow for
Higgsfield and Claude to talk together,
essentially. And then it should go ahead
and say that you are connected, which is
great. And now Claude can basically
control Higgsfield. So, when you say,
"Hey Claude, can you make me an image?"
Claude will basically just go in here,
and it will do it for you. "Hey Claude,
can you go to the marketing studio? It
will just do it for you. So, it's super
cool. So, let's build that website that
I talked about. What we're going to do
is we're going to go to this GitHub
repo. We're going to just copy the URL
of the repo.
And we're going to go into Claude and
paste that in. So, it's really just a
URL. GitHub is basically just a place to
like store code and you can share code
with people and you can work on things
together. So, this person made this
repo, this project, public. So, we can
basically just use it which is awesome.
So, now you're going to say something
like this.
Okay. So, the first thing I want to do
is set up a website for our business,
Perk Form.
Inside of this project, you already have
things like our logo, our brand
guidelines, some product shots. I want
you to think carefully from a design
perspective,
how can we actually use all of those
logos and things, as well as the Scroll
World GitHub repo that I just linked in
here, use them together to create a
super premium and professional, but also
interactive and fun um website for us.
Now, look at our three P's, look at our
personas and things, and make sure that
you're designing the copy and you're
designing the structure of the site in a
way that appeals to our target person,
in a way that shows how we're solving
their pain with our business promise,
and then just go ahead and give me that
website. And so, now we're just going to
shoot that off and we're going to let
Claude cook on that. Because it has all
the context that we gave it earlier,
right? Because that's where you get into
the territory of websites feeling very
generic and bland if you don't give it
all of this stuff. We've given it
context on our business and we've also
given it a bunch of assets. So, we
should get something that comes back
that feels super branded. Now, let's see
if it has any questions for us. You can
see that it's going to read the brand
guidelines, look at the Scroll World
repo, and check what Hicksfield can
actually host. So, just kind of keep
your eyes on this. It's going to go to
work. It's going to do some things and
make some commands and I'll check back
in with you guys once we have something
to review. Okay, so the website came
back and it's done and I'll open it up
in a sec to show you guys. I know you
can see a little preview on the right,
but I just wanted to call out how it got
here. So, it said, "Hey, the design. I
pulled the system straight from your
guidelines PDF rather than inventing
one. So, that's how we can see it has
our logo and our colors and things like
that. It opens on the pain, not the
product. We have the morning path. We
have all of the stuff, all the business
context that we gave it. And so now,
here is the actual website. You can see
we have a little bit of an animation in
the back. It says, "Your morning
shouldn't require two drinks." So,
that's like the pain right away that we
talked about earlier. Now, if I start to
scroll down, we're going to get a few
different things to happen. The first
thing that we see is you are buying two
drinks. On the left, we see coffee. On
the right, we see protein. And as I
scroll, these sort of merge together,
and then we have our vanilla latte perk
form. So, we built one instead of two.
And then as we scroll more, the text
changes to one can and you're out the
door. So, that fits the context that we
gave it earlier. Now, if we keep
scrolling down, we can see there's 11
minutes before you leave. We have to go
through like the shower, find the keys,
answer one email, make breakfast, and
grab our coffee, and then we go. And so,
whether you like this vibe so far or
not, you can obviously come back and
give it more feedback. But what I can
tell you is that this is more unique
than a typical AI vibe coded site on the
first pass, right? You have to assume
things are not usually going to be
perfect on the first prompt. But for
this being one prompt, not too bad.
Anyways, this is some information we'd
have to fill out because it doesn't
currently know we didn't give it these
nutrition facts. But anyways, now we get
into the three main flavors. And here we
get the scroll animation. So, bold
mocha. As we scroll, we get this
close-up in the back of a bold mocha
can. It's got condensation on the side.
We see some drips going down. Super
cool. We continue down to the vanilla
latte. We see this one spinning a little
bit. And these are all C dance 2.5
videos that Higgsfield created. All of
these videos you're seeing were created
with Higgsfield. And Claude knew how to
build this site so that when you scroll,
the
um clips actually sort of like play
forward. And then finally, the last one
down here, we have the salted caramel,
as you can see. And then that's
basically the end of the site. It feels
very on brand though, and it doesn't
feel super AI vibe coded. Now, I know
you guys can't see the URL, but up here
it says localhost 8931. So, a localhost
basically just means that this is an app
that's currently running on your
computer locally. So, if you try to copy
and paste that URL to your laptop or to
someone else, they wouldn't see this.
So, your next step here is you have to
get this somewhere that can be actually
hosted and where it can be accessible to
the public. And that's actually a super
super easy process. I don't want to
waste time in this video, but I've made
so many different YouTube videos where
I've covered that. So, I'll tag one of
those right up here, which you can just
follow along. All you have to do is
connect your codebase to GitHub, and
then it pushes to GitHub, and then it
pushes to Vercel. It's super easy. I
know it sounds a little complicated, but
trust me, it'll take like 5 minutes, and
you'll completely understand what it's
doing. All right. So, now that you guys
have seen the magic of connecting Claude
with all that context to Higgsfield, and
we saw that beautiful site that it
created for us, let me just show you off
a few other use cases that you can do
here that don't require you to know much
about video creation or image creation.
So, a couple use cases. This first one
that I'm going to shoot off is for ad
creatives. So, I'm just going to come
into the same chat, and we can run all
these at the same time, which I'm going
to show you. And I'm going to say,
"Hey, so we have a huge sale coming up.
We're going to do a BOGO offer, so a buy
one box get one box free, and that will
come for, you know, boxes of all three
flavors mixed, or you can buy just one
flavor individually. So, I need you to
generate a bunch of different ad
creatives for this so that we can test
just like a ton of different creatives.
Um different copy, different images,
just different ad creatives that we can
run. So, I want you to do this with
Higgsfield using our, you know, brand
context. And importantly, at the end,
when you finished up, I need you to
actually tell me how much this costed.
And throw this into a folder in the
output folder that's labeled for our
summer BOGO offer. Okay, so that one's
going to get busy. I'm going to go ahead
and spin up another one, because we can
just keep generating all these different
things. I'm going to come back at the
end, show the deliverables, and show how
much each one costed. So, this next one
we want to do, let's say we just want to
do like a fun marketing sort of like
sizzle reel. Hey, so I need you to use
Higgsfield and create me a sizzle reel.
I want you to do this using Higgs Field
Marketing Studio because this thing lets
you create things with music and it's
fast-paced and it's energetic and it has
cool edits and stuff like that. So, I
just want you to make sort of like a
viral sizzle reel that we can put on our
websites or on our different socials.
So, that should be done for our Perk
Form product. Let's also go ahead and
just do an example for Instagram
carousels, for example. Hey, so we're
trying to launch Perk Form's Instagram
presence and right now we just need a
few carousels. I just want a few that
talk to our target audience about like,
"Hey, why did we create this product?
And who is it for? And what problems do
it does it solve? And the different
flavors and things like that." So, just
give me a few different Instagram posts.
Um you know, get creative here and tell
me what you think would be good posts
that we could maybe pin on our Instagram
profile and stuff like that. And once
you've generated all of this, save it in
the correct folder in the correct spot
in our project as well as tell me how
much this costed. So, now that I've shot
off three prompts, you're kind of
understanding the vibe, right? It's
going to know to use Higgs Field, it's
going to know to use our business
context, it takes care of the rest, but
I'm basically just talking to this thing
like I would a human. I'm saying the
motivation, I'm saying the end goal, I'm
saying where to keep stuff, and I'm also
just saying, "Hey, tell me how much this
costed." And finally, let's do one more
with like UGC ads. Hey, so we want to
push um Perk Form a little bit more
organically on our socials and we want
to get some UGC video ads created. So,
what I'm looking for are for you to
create me a few different generations of
UGC ads. They should be vertical for
social media and they should be just
basically
very, very organic feeling videos of
people who are, you know, holding the
products, reviewing it, saying what they
like about it. They should obviously fit
our target person and they should answer
the pain that we're trying to solve.
They should just feel super
um
super seamless. Some of them can be a
little more edited, some can be maybe
just a raw take, but just give me a few
different variations that I can see
what's possible with UGC ads um video
ads. You can use C Dance 2.5 for this if
you want, but if you want to try a few
other models, go for it. So, you guys
remember earlier I mentioned how one of
the big advantages of Claude besides the
context and the guidelines which you
guys have been seeing
the skills.
What we can do now is when this stuff
comes back whether it's our sizzle reel
or our ad creators or whatever it is if
we liked it we can turn that into a
skill. So then that way oh you know
every time that you create an ad like
this
use this skill. All right so all of
these assets have finished up. I'm going
to walk you through all the deliverables
and the price of each but let me just
show you real quick the files because
obviously if we open up the files and we
go to output we now have a lot of
things. We have our ads we have our
social we have our UGC our video and if
we want to do web we have this is where
our website is but let me just open it
up in here to show you what it actually
created. So in the output we have all
these folders right and the first one
that we did were ads. So if I click into
the ads we have our summer BOGO and this
is its own folder. So next time you run
this and you have a different promotion
or a different set of ads it'll create a
new folder. But in here you can see
we've got images we've got V1 backup
we've got ad copy and we've got run
notes. So let me just show you all of
these ads that it created. Okay so here
are all of them. It did a total of I
think it was 18. So let's take a look
real quick.
Here we have two drinks one can. We have
the fonts we have the color scheme it
says buy one box get one free. We have
the two drinks equals one can. We even
have like a little ruler style
grid on the left hand side.
I like this one. High quality you can
see that the images of the actual
products always look consistent as well.
We have buy one box get one free mixed
flavors or all in one. We have breakfast
optional with the vanilla latte flavor
BOGO. Stock the whole summer buy one box
get one free. So obviously every single
one of these is going to say somewhere
BOGO in some form.
Can't pick don't mix box two for one. We
have gym bag to desk the shaker stays
clean. We've got the um
uh the ruler thing again. I think it's
because like shaker bottles protein
right? We've got same habit more return.
Cold case handled. Bold mocha doubled.
So here you guys can see these are all
very high quality images and they have
the branding they have our color schemes
because we have the brand guidelines. It
understands the messaging, it
understands the target audience super
super well, and then also created some
down here that were just blank in case
we wanted to add in our own copy. And
what's cool about this is we have all of
these saved now. So, if we wanted to run
another promotion cycle, we don't have
to generate all of these again. We can
see which ones work best, and we can
just change up the call to action, or we
can just change up the copy. Or vice
versa, we could say, "Oh, I really
really like this copy, same habit more
return. Let's put this copy on all 18 of
these graphics and then run those again
as ad creatives." And it's funny because
I didn't add any subject matter
expertise. If you've been running ads
for a while, or if you have good
knowledge of like what makes a good
creative and what makes a good copy,
then apply that subject matter expertise
to your prompts, and it will be even
better. I literally just said, "Hey,
create me some ads for BOGO." You know,
that's all I said. And all of these 18
cost us $3.43.
So, really not too bad, especially
because we can reuse these and we don't
have to like do full regenerations
later. If we wanted to have like a bunch
of these that are just kind of like
blank with no copy, and then we could
add the copy later. So, the one honest
thing I will say about Higgsfield is not
the cheapest tool out there for all of
these different models, but it has
everything aggregated into one spot, and
it's got other things that are really
cool like the marketing studio, which I
want to show you guys next. The
marketing studio is super super cool.
Let me just pull up that video that it
made. So, if I go into the files and we
go to our output, we go to our video,
and we go to the sizzle reel, let me
show you it did a vertical one and it
did a um
landscape one. So, let me just show you
these real quick. They're super good.
I mean, those are insane. I think the
only thing I noticed was this logo
wasn't exactly correct, but
this took no creativity from me and it
has all of these different scenes, it
has all of the music, the elements, the
copy. This is so good. Do you know how
long this would have taken you to be
able to do manually and how much effort
goes into something like that? I'm just
that's very impressive to me. But
unfortunately, to generate something
like that it's not as cheap as three
bucks. This one was like 17.55
cents based on my credits. So, video is
obviously going to be more expensive
than um images, but for the cost of like
hiring a developer or sorry, hiring a
video editor to do something like that,
it would cost you way more than just 20
bucks. Okay, so the next ones that we
had were carousels. It ended up creating
five different carousels for us. So,
let's just go through these real quick.
All of these obviously have the same
like branding feel because our brand
guidelines and it knows our positioning.
So, your morning shouldn't require two
drinks. Coffee happens because coffee
always happens. Protein is the maybe two
purchases, two things to carry. So, we
put them in one can. Same habit, one
less stop, three flavors of coffee.
Coffee that pulls its weight. Okay, so
I'm not going to read out the caption of
every single one. I'm kind of just going
to scroll through here, but you guys can
see the vibe that we're going for. You
can see the way that these carousels are
styled. If you really, really liked any
of these or you really disliked any of
these, you'd say, "Hey, I loved carousel
two. Let's make a scale around that
one." So, I can do that style again. Or
I don't like carousel three, you know,
let's never, ever have them like that
again. But as far as the images, the
pictures, you can see that the cans are
coming through the same and we're
getting a really nice vibe here. And
once again, we didn't have to say
anything besides go make me different
variations, go make me different angles.
This one is showing off the different
flavors. It's really going to help you
just volume negates luck, right? So, the
more creatives you can make, the more
carousels you can make, the more ads you
can make, the more content you can make,
the more likely you are that you're
going to hit. And once you put stuff out
there, you have the data. And now you
can see what's working, what doesn't
work, and you can use that to iterate
and make things even better. Because
think about how powerful this is. After
you have Claude with Higgsfield making
all the assets, you can connect it to
the actual performance data, and you can
have it every week review what it made,
review what did well, and make more that
did well. And you can just keep the
cycle going. You can keep the momentum
going. So, all of these carousels, this
was, you know, $9.56.
We had five carousels
that were each about like seven to eight
slides. So, that was a lot of
generations and it cost us just about 10
bucks. Okay, so now for the UGC ads, but
I really need you guys to appreciate
what it did here. Because this one was
the most expensive, but it did a lot.
So, I'm going to go back into the
folder. I'm going to go to output. I'm
going to go to our UGC. And we have UGC
ads that we generated on 8/20, so August
20th. But let's look in here.
We have boards, creators, QA, and video.
So, I just want to show you what it did
here. The first thing it did is it
created images of characters. So, we
have these four characters. This is the
first one. This is the second one. This
is the third one. And this is the fourth
one. And so, we can now reuse these
characters, or in the future we can keep
generating new ones. So, if you want to
have like a consistent character that is
always on your page, that's like your
brand avatar, then you can just reuse
this character every single time. And
then after it created all those
creators, it went ahead and made boards.
So, it created these boards here, which
helped the video generation be like more
in control of the story. So, you can see
she is standing here filming like selfie
style. There's a coffee cup and a
protein shake. And then she opens this.
There's a close-up. She drinks it. And
now we have all of these boards laid
out. So, the video generation can just
be, like I said, way more in control
because it's planned out with images
first with the characters, and then
videos are generated. So, let's go ahead
and take a look at the actual videos.
Oh, and by the way, it also did a QA
pass, so quality assurance. Meaning it
went through the videos and it took
screenshots and it took these videos.
So, for example, in the QA it found this
one that it had generated, but it
rejected it. And it says back panel, so
I'm assuming there was some text that
was off or a logo that was off, or
something.
>> Bottom shelf, back row. Where protein
shakes go to be ignored.
Swap that for protein coffee.
>> So, I'm not sure if it was something
here that it noticed.
>> Coffee that pulls
>> But, the point being, it goes through
and it checked on all the stuff to
verify that it was okay before it told
me that it was finished. Okay, so now
let's take a look at those finished
outputs.
>> Coffee in one hand, protein shake in the
other. Both going cold on the counter.
That's the morning this replaces.
Protein coffee, sealed and cold, no
blender. Coffee that pulls its weight.
>> So, it's very realistic, right? You can
kind of tell it's an AI avatar still,
but the thing that I don't like about
these is that they are still very like
ad. Like they're very salesy in a way.
You can tell it's not completely
organic. And so, that would be on us to
actually have it go analyze some other
UGC content or create some scripts that
we approve, and then we shoot over the
scripts and the storyboards for video
generation. But, let's watch like one or
two more.
>> 11 minutes before you leave the house.
Enough time for coffee.
Not enough for anything you'd call
breakfast.
So, the shake stays in the cabinet and
the day starts short.
This is coffee. Protein's already in it.
Cold, sealed, one hand, out the door.
Real coffee, and it's doing two jobs
instead of one. Coffee that pulls its
weight.
>> And the thing is, these are kind of like
engaging because they're very cut up,
right? Like it's two-second clip,
one-second clip, two-second clip. You
don't have to do it that way. You could
have it be like, you know, just a
15-second raw selfie-style video, but it
wanted to cut these up. And like I said,
for those generations, they did eat up
more time because they were longer,
because they also had to have images and
storyboards created and more QA passes.
But, when you think about the ROI, if
you can pump out content like this, it's
truly nothing. Okay, so that was just me
showing you guys off some use cases.
Obviously, there's a lot more you need
to do. You need to dive in a little bit,
add more of your own touch, add some
more research, because you can't just
expect to throw one prompt out there and
then go viral and go make a million
dollars. But that was me showing you how
much you can do with just a few prompts
before you actually even really dig in.
So let me know down below what you guys
would like to see me more specifically
build some really good skills around and
then make some videos on. But now I
think what you should do is something
like this to track your generations,
because obviously you're going to be
able to in here track everything in the
output folder, but it might start to get
a little bit messy and maybe you want a
better UI to actually look at the stuff.
So I think the answer really is just
have a simple Google Sheet or a simple
Excel Sheet where you can see all these
generations and maybe you can even throw
in ideas. And then later Claude can come
in here and update it with like the
views and the engagements or even maybe
the conversions on those specific
videos. Hey Claude, so we just went
through four rounds of generations. We
did BOGO ad creatives, we did sizzle
reel, we did carousels, and we did UGC
content. What I want you to do now is
create me an Excel Sheet that shows, you
know, the date, the type of generation
we ran, um if you can put the outputs in
there that would be great as well. And
then maybe just give me like the core
angle we were using, because every time
that we are creating different um types
of content or creatives, we typically
have some sort of angle and then later I
want to be able to analyze like what
angles worked best, what copy worked
best, things like that. So just give me
basically an Excel Sheet with analytics
that we can continue to grow over time
and use that to help make better
decisions in the future. And so now that
thing is going to go look through all
those sessions, go look through our
outputs, make us that Excel Sheet, and
I'll check back in when that is done. So
that finished up. It took about 8
minutes and you can see that it once
again it threw this in our file. So if I
go over here, files, output, we have a
new one that it created, a new folder
called analytics, and now we have this
creative tracker. So let me go ahead and
open this up from here. And this is
pretty cool.
It even made this Excel Sheet using our
brand guidelines. It literally made the
color scheme over here
like with these bold lime green sort of
colors. It did the same thing with the
tabs down here cuz normally when I make
Excel sheets with Claude, it does not do
this. So, it definitely used our design
system, our brand guidelines to make
this, which is kind of funny. So,
anyways, this first page walks us
through what the tabs are. We have a
generation log, so we can see we have
different IDs, we can have the date, we
have the generation type, the campaign,
the channel, primary angle, angles
covered, we have deliverables, we have
Jen's build, so how many generations we
were billed for, the tool and the model,
so Nano Banana Pro. Um this one was the
marketing studio. This one was GPT image
2.0. This was a bunch of different
things, Soul, GPT image, and Seed Dance
2.5. How many credits it all costed, how
much actual dollars that was, and then
we have the status. So, every time we
have more generations, we can tell it to
update the sheet. We could also build
some automations in here so that it's
constantly doing that, it's going
through a sweep and always updating. We
could also drop ideas in here and be
like, "Hey, check the sheet and go
process anything that's new." We could
have automatic research that goes in
here. Every week it's scraping different
creatives and then putting ideas in
here. There's so much that you can do
once you have this system in Claude,
which you guys now should all have. We
have creative assets, as you can see,
which is basically each of the images
and videos with a supporting copy. We
can have the angle performance, so we
can start to put more info in here with
analytics. We have the copy bank and we
have the cost summary. So, you can
customize this as you want. Obviously,
once again, I was pretty vague and I
just said, "Hey, give us this Excel
sheet." But, you can obviously iterate
on this and make changes as you need.
So, that was basically what I want to
show you guys today. We have set up our
project, we have set up our brand. We
talked about connecting Higgs Field, we
talked about generating assets, and most
importantly, we talked about why we
wanted to actually connect Higgs Field
to Claude. It's so that we could get our
business context in there, our skills,
and our guidelines. But anyways, guys,
if you like the way I teach and you want
to dive deeper into this stuff, I
dropped a free 6-hour Claude Code course
for non-coders, which you can access
right up here, or I guess it'll be right
up here. Go ahead, watch that 6-hour
course, and just keep building up your
Cloud Code projects. Keep building up
your marketing teams. I hope to see you
guys over there.